

CONTACT

- +55 43 9 8869 8502
- imbianchi.dev
- linkedin.com/in/imbianchi
- github.com/imbianchi

HARD SKILLS

- NodeJS
- ReactJS
- Solidity
- Solana
- Rust
- VueJS
- AWS
- Azure

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Flexible
- Problem Solving
- Decision Making
- Critical Thinking

EDUCATION

2022 - 2024 POSITIVO UNIVERSITY

Computer Systems Analisys

LANGUAGES

• English



JOÃO BIANCHI

- SOFTWARE DEVELOPER -

PROFILE

Software Developer - JS | Solidity | Solana | Rust

Open to exciting opportunities in web development focused in web3, and continuous learning.

Software Developer & Lifelong learner.

Building path to Web3, Cyber Security & Rust Specialist.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ExxonMobil

2022 - 2023

Developer Tools Analyst

Microsoft Azure, ADO, Windows Server, Windows Runners, GitHub Cloud, GitHub Server, GitHub Actions, NodeJS, ReactJS, VueJS, REST API's, Python automation scripts, MSSQL, TFVC, TFS among others.

Bis2Bis

2021 - 2022

Scrum Master/Tech Lead

PHP, Magento 2, NodeJS, ReactJS, Linux, NGINX, AWS. Huawei, Bash, Docker. Orchestrated Scrum ceremonies, organized events, and liaised directly with PO's. Provided hands-on guidance & support to the development squad. Collaborated with the architecture team to migrate stores from AWS to Huawei.

Antena 1

2020 - 2021

Web Developer

Most used techs & tools: NodeJS, ReactJS (JSX), Redux, ImmutableJS, REST, GitHub, Webviews, Webpack. KnexJS, Plesk, WordPress, Scrum, Code Reviewer, JWT, Cookies, Cache, MariaDB, ExpressJS, SASS among others.

SENAI/SESITECH

2018 - 2020

Web/App Developer

Most used techs & tools: NodeJS, ReactJs, React Native, REST, OOP. API integrations, GitLab, Redmine, Scrum, HapiJS, JWT, AES256, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, CI/CD, among others.

CODESTACK

2017 - 2018

Web WP Developer

Most used techs & tools: jQuery, JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, CSS, HTML, Woocommerce, Scrum GitHub.

HOBBIES

Movies/Cinema

Drums

- Piano
- Read
- Coding
- Barbecue with friends